{
    "subject": "Archduke_Gottfried_of_Austria",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Princess_Dorothea_of_Bavaria",
    "human_readable": "Archduke Gottfried of Austria is married to Princess Dorothea of Bavaria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9741653800010681,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Archduke Gottfried and Princess Dorothea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.971886157989502,
            "question": "Is Archduke Gottfried of Austria married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9698269963264465,
            "question": "Who is Archduke Gottfried of Austria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9156338572502136,
            "question": "Who is Archduke Gottfried of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8692164421081543,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Archduke Gottfried and Princess Dorothea?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7605594992637634,
            "question": "What is the name of Archduke Gottfried's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5354490280151367,
            "question": "To which royal family does Princess Dorothea belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37661194801330566,
            "question": "What is the name of Princess Dorothea's country of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36799606680870056,
            "question": "Where did Princess Dorothea grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16966576874256134,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Archduke Gottfried of Austria is married to Princess Dorothea of Bavaria.",
            "html": "yago_31398_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Princess Dorothea grow up?",
            "html": "yago_31398_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Princess Dorothea's country of origin?",
            "html": "yago_31398_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which royal family does Princess Dorothea belong?",
            "html": "yago_31398_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31398_61.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the evaluation result:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Archduke Gottfried of Austria married Princess Dorothea of Bavaria on August 2, 1938 (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_31398/re-ranker-msmarco/19.txt). This confirms the triple \"Archduke Gottfried of Austria is married to Princess Dorothea of Bavaria\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple instances where Archduke Gottfried of Austria is mentioned as being married to Princess Dorothea of Bavaria, including details such as the date and place of their marriage."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}